「ミニチュアローズ」によって 王と共に爆死した
This is it. My brother sent the URL. Great! Let's get started.
王！
to face the Phantom Troupe
and avenge the Kurta, Gon and Killua also prepare for the auction
あっ！ あっ！
in Yorknew City.
あぁ…！ 息がある！
This is the website for Hunters?
だが　チクショ！ 早くしないと王が！
Yeah, I've heard that Hunters
worldwide post information here. Worldwide?
間に合わねえ！
Wow...
とてもピトーまでは 王が持たねえよ！ 大丈夫　私が王を救う！
Please swipe your Hunter License, and enter your license code.
私を召し上がっていただく。 それだけのこと。
Put the cursor on the bartender. What kind of information would you like?
あっ…。
Wow! There's so much! Select the game category.
あっ…　あぁ…。
It will cost twenty million Jenny.
さぁ　私の細胞達よ！
Twenty million... So they won't give out the
information for free.
隅々まで行きわたり　王を癒やせ！
Well, we don't really have a choice. Deposit twenty million...
お　お　お…。
One person who owned the game
王！
hired fifty Hunters to give it a shot, but none of them ever came back.
王。
I hear that you can return
if you find a save point. Is that true?
いかがですか？　ご気分は。
This information is from
the Hunter website. It's gotta be accurate.
えも言えぬ美味。
At the Yorknew City auction, seven copies of Greed Island
will be up for sale.
楽園の空気を吸うがごとく
The lowest starting bid is 8.9 billion Jenny.
力が　見る見る 満ちて来るのが分かる。
8.9 billion?! The price has shot up!
まさに　妖精のミスト。
That's 3 billion more than the retail price! Difficulty of obtainment is G-rank. Huh?
なんと…
The game is considered a legend, but there are plenty of copies.
なんと… もったいないお言葉！
If you have enough money,
it's relatively easy to procure. Hmm, a G...
うっ！　うぅ…。
Lower than I expected.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。 それは　よろしゅうございました。
The message is that if I can't
even get a simple game, I'll never be able to find you, Ging.
存分にお召し上がりくださいませ。 たっぷりと用意してあります。
Still, the money is a big problem.
はぁ…　あっ。
Hey, can we participate in the auction?
たまらぬ…。
They're starting at 8.9 billion!
この味を…　知ってしまっては…
That's out of our league. No, I mean by selling stuff. Selling?
もう…　他のものは
That's it! We can look for treasure,
and then auction it off.
食えぬではないか。
Okay! We can start with the 800 million we earned
あぁ！
at Heavens Arena, and go from there. Yep!
あぁ！ 王！　王！　王！　王！
First, we'll start with online flea
markets and auction websites. And see what we can dig up.
もう　これ以上　私を 喜びの天空へと　いざなうのは おやめください！
We'll increase our money,
and get ourselves a copy of Greed Island ! Yeah!
王！　それでは こちらも　ご賞味ください！
Yay!
細胞を液体に変えて…
I couldn't help it! Only the risky sites are profitable.
くっ…　考えたな　ユピー
It isn't working...
おぉ…　おぉ…。
Now, show me what you've brought.
おおお…。
The hair of the famous actress Sara, and a DNA test to validate authenticity.
おぉ…。
The right arm of an Egyptian mummy,
taken directly from a pyramid.
おぉ…！
The scaly skin of an ichthyosis patient.
なんと力強く濃厚な…。
Okay, all four of you are hired. I'm Dalzollene, the head bodyguard.
天界から 降り落ちたとしか思えぬ…。
It's a pleasure. I'll need you to start working immediately.
まさに　天使の滴！ あぁ！
Your mission is to escort the boss
to a Yorknew City hotel room.
おぉ！　おぉ！
The trip between airport and hotel takes approximately ninety minutes.
あぁ！
A special car has been prepared.
王！
You four will provide the
outer ring of security. Any questions?
くっ…。
Do you know who might
be targeting the boss?
共に極上の一品と断ずるに
The boss is an important
figure in the underworld. There are plenty of people with
reasons to hold a grudge.
迷いの余地は皆無。
Let me rephrase since you
didn't understand the first time.
あっ！ あぁ…！
Regardless of grudges, do you know
足りぬ…　もっとだ。
anyone who might actually
commit to an attack?
両方とも…。
If we can identify a few candidates, we'll know
their motives, styles, and circumstances, and we can prepare accordingly.
ありったけ…　持ってまいれ…。
That will facilitate protecting the boss. You said that your name is Kurapika?
うおぉ！
Our job is to protect the boss, no matter who, when,
where, or how they attack.
あぁ！
That's all you need to know!
はい！ わが王！
Don't bother building a mental profile.
喜んで！
If anything comes too close, it's hostile.
この上ない至高 極上の喜び
I'll introduce you to the boss. Come with me.
これは何だ!? この気持ちは!?
He ignored my advice, and let himself be deceived
by false information, placing not only the other bodyguards,
but the boss in danger as well.
これからは　余を
So he was punished. You are replacing him.
「メルエム」と呼ぶがいい。
Let's go.
それこそ
Boss, I've brought the new bodyguards.
母より賜りし　余の名前。
Please enter.
絶対的存在の死と再生に際し さらに　自身を 王と共有することによって
No kidding... They called her an important
figure in the underworld, so I was expecting someone intimidating, but she turned out to be a cute little girl.
以前の王より明らかに！
You guys are going with us, too? Yo!
我々の肉体が お役に立ったのだ
Haven't seen your faces in a while.
そして　王の一部に
I'm here, chief.
何という光栄！ 何という至福！
What's our target this time? Give us our orders!
王の意識まで 共有しているかのよう！
Feitan's group won't arrive until evening. We'll wait until everyone's here. You have no patience.
しかし…
Oh? Is that Shizuku?
だからこそ分かる
Hello.
王は　今…
Has the other new addition arrived yet? No idea...
先ほどの料理も　お望みとあれば まだ　ございます。
This is for September.
あと数分で 私の分身も　ここに来る 料理…。
Huh? So many? Yeah, Rotfelli-sama and Trinc-sama
would like their fortunes told.
そうか…。
That just sucks.
あの味は現実か。
I told you to stop increasing my workload. I apologize.
まばゆい光の中で
And what's Daddy doing?
何者かが余の名前を呼んだ。
He had to attend a meeting. He's probably off playing golf or hunting.
「メルエム」と。
Daddy? This is Neon.
なぜ
Fine, you have to keep your word.
余が　ここにいるのか…。
If you break another promise, I'll quit.
思い出せぬ。
Yay! I get another piece of treasure!
あっ！
A sweet deal.
メルエム様…。
Since that's settled, I'll get this over with.
気分は悪くない。 いや…　むしろ 全身に力が　みなぎっている。
Angelic Auto Writing
Lovely Ghostwriter
我々の分身を 偵察に出しております。 敵の残党を捜し出し 始末するため…。
I hear she's an incredible diviner. Thanks to her father's connections, she's made clients of some very
important people in the underworld.
うっ！ あっ！
No, it's the other way around. Other way around?
たとえ　余をおもんぱかってのこと だとしても
I'd say that the father has used
his daughter to increase his standing in the underworld.
余に対する偽りは　背信と心得よ。
That's why he is frightened of losing her.
もう　二度は言わぬぞ。
Afraid that his enemies might strike back at his daughter.
余は　食ったのだな？
Okay, all done. Here. Excellent work.
お主達を。 我々が 差し出したのでございます！
Say, tomorrow's auction starts at night, right?
差し出がましいまねとは知りつつ 全て我々の一存！
I want to do some shopping beforehand. Very well, I shall accompany you.
私とユピーの　もともとの姿は 覚えておいでのご様子。
How many years has it been
ならば　我々が初めて 王にお仕えした日のことは？
since all thirteen Troupe members gathered, Feitan? Three years, two months. However, two members have since changed.
分からぬ。
#4 and #8 are now different people.
お主達が護衛軍 プフとユピーであることは
Machi, will #4, Hisoka, actually show up today?
見た瞬間に認識できた。
No idea.
いや…　正確には 思い出したというべきか。
Don't ask me. Wasn't he your responsibility? I was only supposed to tell him to come.
だが　前後の経緯となると 記憶がない。
I don't like Hisoka.
メルエム様。
Why does the chief let
him do as he pleases? Because he has skills.
恐らく　爆発の衝撃による
Skills, huh?
一時的な 記憶障害でございましょう。
His Bungee Gum is quite impressive.
爆発…。 はい。
It would be difficult to counter.
王は 自ら敵と　１対１の決闘に臨み
What's your point? Are you claiming that the
chief is afraid of Hisoka?
ここへ来ました。
I won't let that statement stand.
しかし　卑劣な人間どもは 強力な爆弾という 汚い手段でもって
That's not what I meant. You're all being too generous.
He's nothing special.
王の誠意に 裏切りで応えたのです！
Talk is cheap, as always.
そう　余は
Nobunaga, this is what happens when I
keep quiet and let you yap.
１対１で戦っていた
You were talking as much as I was, Franklin.
王の生命力　運命力を もってすれば
And so it begins. Ignore them.
人間ごときの兵器で致命傷を 受ける道理はございません。
They're just playing around again. Anyway, why is the chief
calling everyone together?
しかし　あまりに 痛ましいお姿を見るに堪えず
We're thieves.
叱責を受けるのは承知の上
There's something he wants us to steal.
微力ながら 回復の一助となった次第。
Well, I know that much.
もともと 我々の体は余す所なく
Yes, we've arrived at the hotel.
王　ご自身が所有されるもの。
However, one of the lady's
fortunes concerned me...
我々は　王にお返しした だけのことでございます。
"An underground chamber
where everything costs extra. That is where you will sleep.
宮殿へ戻りましょう。
Never descend stairs that
you didn't first ascend.
それが 記憶回復の早道にございます。
Do not compete with others at numbers." There were three other poems
that begin with this verse.
これは…
Meaning that all four clients
received the same fortune.
千載一遇の
The only thing connecting them
チャンス！
is that they will be attending the
underground auction this year.
ひと足先に宮殿へ戻り… あれを始末する
So the fortune is saying that
their lives are at risk, should they participate?
今ならば 王に　あれの記憶はない
I'm assuming that "sleep" is a metaphor for succumbing to illness or death.
今ならば あれの存在を消してしまえば 思い出す機会もなくなる理屈！
I understand. I will pass the fortunes on to the clients. One more thing.
やることは ピトーの説得？
The lady never remembers
the fortunes she's told, and she cannot tell her own fortune.
邪魔な人間どもの排除？ いや！　まず…
Does it make sense to let her
participate in the auction? No!
何よりも…
Bring her back immediately!
あれの息の根を止める
However, I will need a proper
explanation, or she'll never listen.
殺ってしまえば 後は　どうとでもなるのです
If she throws a tantrum,
we won't be able to stop her. In any case, don't take her
to the auction site.
王が　これから 宮殿に向かうとして
Send some bodyguards to place bids.
全力で走っても ２０分は　かかる
I understand.
おぉ！
The sun's about to rise. Damn Hisoka...
生まれた時から　我が身の 一部だったかのような自然さ。
Next time I see him, I'll tear him apart.
すぐにでも飛べる。
Oh, dear...
あぁ…！ あっ…。
How very scary. Hisoka, you bastard!
宮殿はどっちだ？
You're late. Man, I thought you weren't going to come.
北です　今の王ならば　急げば １５分ほどで着きましょう！
You asked me to come...
ある。
Chief, everyone's here.
速い！ もたもたしてたら追い付かれる １５分？ いや　このスピードなら
There will be multiple copies of the
most expensive game ever for sale. Wouldn't it be logical to take
precious metals and gemstones? Everything.
５分で着いてしまう 猶予は長くて２３分 急げ！　私の分身！
We're taking everything
that's up for auction.
これは賭けだ 宮殿の前に整然と並ぶ 数百万の人の群れを見れば
Are you serious, chief? The underground auction is run by
gangs from across the world.
王は　きっと思い出してくださる
If we do that, we'll be making
enemies of them all...
生物統一こそ 唯一無二の目的だと！
Are you frightened, Uvogin? I'm thrilled!
あの小娘さえ 目に入らなければ！
I'm shaking with excitement... Give us the command, chief!
護衛軍として！
Right now!
消去する！ 下賤な　ヒトの娘など！
You have my permission... Kill them.
「ハコワレ」！
Good work. I have your next assignment.
繭になる前に。
Complete with DNA validation. And...
どこにいても 私には手に取るように見える。
The eyeballs of a Kurta, also known as scarlet eyes.
何だ!?　今 私の分身を攻撃したものは!? プフ　何だ？　それは。
Also, we've received information that
there will be an attack on the auction. Prepare for any unexpected complications, while focusing on the primary
objective of obtaining these items.
私の分身が　敵の残党に 反撃された結果のようです。
They're coming. They are definitely coming!
急ぐぞ。
Kurapika awaits his chance
to avenge his brethren.
王は…！
of the auction, where all sides will soon clash.